mts.com 2011-01-03

# MTS: Testing Systems, Sensor Solutions, Simulation Systems

|  | 

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**MTS RESPECTS YOUR RIGHT TO PRIVACY**

A user of the Internet is presented with inherent privacy risks. For this reason, MTS believes that you, the Site user, be informed how MTS collects and uses information provided or collected at its Web site (“Site”). Wherever possible, MTS tries to provide the user with opportunities to review and change any personal information that is collected. 

This statement describes privacy practices which apply to the MTS Web Site, www.MTS.com. Please note that this Site may contain links to external web sites over which MTS maintains no control and therefore takes no responsibility regarding privacy considerations or content. This Privacy Policy is subject to updates at any time.

**BY ACCESSING AND USING THE SITE, THE USER IS CONSENTING TO THE COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION AS DISCUSSED IN THIS POLICY.

SUMMARY OF INFORMATION THAT MTS GATHERS ONLINE

**  
MTS collects two types of information from users who access our Site: (1) information gathered by analyzing page views and user navigation patterns; and (2) information that users provide directly when they use various MTS services or participate in various MTS programs.

**  
HOW MTS USES THE INFORMATION GATHERED ONLINE**  
It uses page view and navigation information to ensure that users can find information on our Site as quickly as possible. It collects demographic information through promotional or survey programs to better identify the products and services that will fulfill users' needs. Further, it uses information collected when users make online purchases to check their qualifications, verify their identity, as well as for billing and shipping purposes. 

Also, MTS does gather information such as analyzing user traffic patterns throughout our Site. It does not attempt to identify individual visitors to our Site, but it may collect data on general types of users based on domain name or browser type. This information is obtained directly from the user's web browser identification information. 

**  
SPECIAL PROGRAMS AND SURVEYS**  
When a user registers for certain MTS programs and services, the user may be asked to provide contact information, demographic information, or billing information. Also, the Site may include surveys in which users are asked to indicate their opinions or preferences. In addition to compiling the responses to survey questions, MTS may use cookies to identify those users who have already participated in a poll. It uses this system to ensure that each respondent's opinion will be represented equally. **

CUSTOMER AND TECHNICAL SUPPORT

**  
MTS uses email as an avenue with which to provide customer service and technical support. It may contact the customer using this information in an attempt to resolve an issue. It may also use the information to proactively notify customers of technical issues which may affect them. **

MTS POLICIES RELATING TO USER INFORMATION

SHARING USER INFORMATION

**  
MTS keeps it customer’s personal information private and does not give it to others, unless permitted by law or to third parties to provide services on our behalf and then only for use for the purposes MTS gave it to them. MTS does not give or sell its customer’s personal information to other companies for marketing purposes unrelated to MTS. **

CORRECTIONS AND UPDATES

**  
MTS offers users the ability to correct or change information during the registration process. **

SITE SECURITY

**  
The MTS Site uses a variety of security measures to prevent the loss, misuse, or alteration of information you send to MTS. MTS uses Secure Sockets Lay (SSL) technology to assure the privacy and security of credit card and other personal data when making an order. SSL uses encryption technology to create a secure connection between your computer and ours. While MTS has put procedures in place to safeguard the information it collects from you, MTS cannot guarantee the security of any information you provide online; you provide it at your own risk!  
  
---|---
